Guide to the Benedict Anderson papers, 1965, 1998
Anderson, Benedict Anderson papers,
- Series I. Indonesia
  - Sudisman: Otokritik, 1967-1970 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    Scanned typescripts (1967; 1970)
  - Sam - Brecht File, 1947-1977 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    Index of biographical information; notes; scanned typescripts (1947-8); scanned news article (1974); correspondence with Ruth McVey(1977); typescripts with marginalia and associated correspondence (1977)
  - Syam Varia Latief, 1949-1984 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    Scanned news article (1984); scanned typescripts (1949; 1978; 1981); notes
  - Trial Materials, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    Scanned typescript (1968); trial reports (1968)
  - Tjakrabirawa materials, 1965-1966 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    Typescript (1965); notes
  - Untung Interrogation and Trials, 1965-1966 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    Trial records (1966); typescript (1965)
  - Utrecht stuff re: coup and background, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    Scanned typescript (1970)
  - Agam Wispi, 1990-1992 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    Bound typescripts (1990-2)
  - Ajip Rosidi, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    Scanned news articles (1964)
  - Ariel Heryanto, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    Scanned typescript (1980)
  - Armijn Pane, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    Scanned typescript (1953)
  - Blora, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    Publication photocopy, some with marginalia (1950); notes
  - Boomgaard Welfare (1900-1942), 1985 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    Typescript draft (1985)
  - Class Notes on Pram, Undated (Box 30, Folder 24)
    Various course notes
  - Emmerson - Ramayana, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    Typescript draft (1973)
  - Foulcher Left Literature, Undated (Box 30, Folder 26)
    Scanned typescripts
  - Gerson, 1970-1995 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    Correspondence (1988); typescript (1970); scanned newspaper clippings (1987); scanned news articles (1995)
  - Howells Thesis on Hinduism, Undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Thesis draft; some marginalia
  - Idrus (Box 31, Folder 2)
    Typescript; scanned news clippings (1941; 1946)
  - Indro Tjahjono, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    Scanned typescript (1979); some marginalia
  - Jejak Langkah, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Photocopy of book draft "naskah belum sempurna" (1975)
  - Kayam etc. Action, 1935-1975 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    Scanned typescripts (1935; 1973; 1975)
  - Linus Suryadi, 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    Scanned typescripts (1981-2); scanned news article (1981)
  - Mas Marco, Undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
    Scanned typescripts, some with accompanying marginalia
  - Nugroho Notosusanto, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    Scanned typescript, draft (1973)
  - Nureholis M. Lenis, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    Reprints (1989)
  - Oeyeng on Islam Abrl, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    Scanned typescript (1969)
  - P. Ario Soerjodiningrat, 1934 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    Scanned typescript (1934)
  - Pemandangan, 1915 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    Photocopies
  - Pram Kids Trans, Undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
    Typescripts; both scanned and unscanned
  - R. Brons Middel: Hikajat Hang Toewah, 1893 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    Photocopy of 1893 publication; some marginalia
  - Rumah Kaca, 1918 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    Photocopy of typescript draft: "Rumah Kaca: Konsep Naskah Belum Sempurna"
  - Tjerita Dari Djakarta, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    Publication photocopy; some marginalia
  - Ken Ward's Stuff on East Java and Islam, 1971-1974 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    Notes; scanned typescripts (1971; 1974)
  - Putu Oka Sukanta Poems, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    Scanned typescripts (1985)
  - Putu Wijaya, 1980-1987 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    Typescripts (1981; 1987); scanned typescript (1980)
  - Rendra, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    Typescripts, scanned and unscanned (1978); scanned news articles (1978); correspondence (1978)
  - Robison, Undated (Box 31, Folder 21)
    Scanned typescript
  - Sjafruddin Prawirauengara, 1951-1969 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    Newspaper clippings (1969); reprints (1951; 1962)
  - Soerjana, 1979-1988 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    Correspondence (1987-8); scanned typescripts (1979; 1985); typescript with marginalia (1979)
  - Sudjarwo, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Sukarno, 1920-1968 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    Various notes; newspaper clippings (1963); image (1920 or 1921); typescript with attached additional notes; scanned typescripts (1958; 1968)
  - Sukarno Speeches, 1959-1965 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    Typescripts (1959; 1965); Interview transcript (1965)
  - Syahrir: pleidooi, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Scanned typescript (1975)
  - Taufik Ismail - Poetry: trans. too, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    Typescripts (1972)
  - Taunus Kemasang, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Typescript drafts (1980)
  - Tiuang Thesis On Chinese, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    Thesis with editorial notes (1979)
  - Warak: Kidung Tatanan Rusak, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    Handwritten and typescript, photocopied
  - Warsodingrat on Gamelan, Undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Yudhis (1), 1977-1984 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Scanned news article; typescript with editorial notes; scanned typescripts
  - Yudhis (2), 1977 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Yudhis AR-3, Undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Yudhis Plays, 1977-1982 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    Typscript (1977; 1981-2)
  - Arnot x Critics Development vs. Equality, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    Typescripts, some scanned (1974)
  - Congressional Hearings Human Rights in Indonesia 1976, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    Photocopy of testimony 1976
  - Crane - Nugan Hand 1982, 1979-1984 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    Scanned news articles (1979; 1980; 1982; 1984); typescript (1984); notes; newspaper clippings (1983)
  - Elections 1971, 1970-1972 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    Scanned typscript (1971); reprint (1972); typscript with editorial marks (1970)
  - Elections 1977, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Governors, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    Typescript (1984)
  - History of Solo, Undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
    Original typed and handwritten notes
  - IGGI, 1988-1992 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    News publication (1990); typescripts (1992)
  - Islam, 1975-1985 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    Scanned typescript (1985); original typed and handwritten notes; scanned dissertation summary (1975)
  - Islamic Terms, Undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
    Notes on vocabulary
  - Labor, 1958-1974 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    Notes (1958-9); table graph
  - Law, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    Notes; typescript (1963)
  - New Order: Advanced Economy, 1967-1991 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    Typescripts (1979 - 1982; 1988; 1991); government publication (1967); newspaper and clippings (1982); scanned news articles (1979; 1980; 1983); journal publications (1976; 1980)
  - New Order Agriculture, 1978-1982 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    Typescripts incl class paper by Beth Rose (1978; 1982); scanned news articles (1979)
  - Oil....., 1977-1978 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    Scanned typescripts (1977); scanned news article (1977)
  - Press, 1962-1986 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    Scanned news articles (1985-6); journal publication (1966); original typescripts (1962-3); interview transcripts (1962)
  - Riots - CJ 1980, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    Scanned news articles (1980); newspapers and clippings (1980)
  - Satire: Cartoons and Lectures (1), Undated (Box 35, Folder 18)
    Scanned articles/cartoons and newspaper clippings; photographs; news publication
  - Satire: Cartoons and Lectures (2), Undated (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Soeharto Personal, 1966-1987 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    Scanned news articles (1972; 1986-7); scanned typescripts (1966; 1982); government documents (1967); reprint (1986); some marginalia
  - Sunda, Undated (Box 35, Folder 21)
    Typescript; scanned image
  - Urban History, Undated (Box 35, Folder 22)
    Original typed notes
  - 1966 Notes, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    Various notes
  - 1969 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    Typescript with some editorial marks (1969)
  - 1972 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    Notes
  - 1973 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - 1974 Miscellaneous, 1974-1977 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    Scanned typescripts (1974-5); typescripts with notes (1974; 1977)
  - 1975 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - 1976 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    Typescripts (1976-7); scanned letter (1976); scanned news articles (1976); original notes "to Ben" by?
  - 1977 Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    Newspaper (1977); original typed notes; typescripts (1977); scanneds news articles (1977)
  - 1978 Crisis, 1977-1979 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    Typescripts (1978-9); notes; scanned news articles (1978); newspapers (1978-9); news publication (1977)
  - 1978 Hearings, 1977-1978 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    Government documents and statements (1978); correspondence (1978); notes; news publication (1977)
  - 1981 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    Scanned news article (1981); notes
  - 1982, 1980-1982 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    Photocopied testimonials, military orders (1980; 1982)
  - 1984 (Box 35, Folder 35)
    Photocopied white paper (Indonesian) "Peristiwa September 84 di Tanjung Priok (1984); scanned news articles (1984)
  - 1985, 1983-1985 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    Scanned news article (1985); photographs (Bukittingi(1985); typescripts (1983; 1985)
  - Atjeh - Materials on Rebellion (HF) (1), 1981-1993 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Reports (INDOC and Amnesty International); scanned typescripts (1951; 1953; 1972); notes; scanned news articles (1955)
  - Atjeh - Materials on Rebellion (HF) (2), 1951-1972 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Bahan Indonesia - Bahasa Prokem, 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    Scanned typescript (1986); scanned news article (1985)
  - Barbara's PRRI - Permesta File, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    Scanned typescript (1971)
  - Biographies, 1952-1969 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    Biographical info; notes; curriculum vitae; scanned news articles (1954); scanned typescripts (1952)
  - Books: Index Prohibitorium, 1985-1988 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    Scanned typescripts (1985; 1988); scanned news articles (1988)
  - Chinese in Indonesia (1), 1951-1981 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    News articles, scanned and otherwise (1966-7; 1979); typescripts (1951; 1965-8; 1981); notes; reprint (1972)
  - Chinese in Indonesia (2), 1951 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    Monograph
  - Elections Materials 1971, 1970-1992 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    Coloured posters; newspapers (1971); table charts (1970) also table chart (1992); typescript (1981)
  - Gelar Ningrat, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    Typescript photocopy (some marginalia) (1987); scanned news articles (1987)
  - Hanes Case, 1985-1987 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    News publication (1987); scanned typescript (1985)
  - Indonesia Death Penalty Bahan, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    Scanned news articles (1979 - 1980)
  - Indonesia: Human Rights, 1967-1994 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    Typescripts (1967; 1988; 1991; 1994); news publications (1982; 1985; 1993); scanned report (1986); notes and brief correspondences
  - Irian Bahar (1), 1965-1988 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    Bulletins (1979; 1988); news publications (1984-5); correspondence (1985); typescripts, some unpublished (1979; 1983-5); scanned news article (1977; 1979; 1984); newspaper clippings (1965; 1969; 1978; 1981)
  - Irian Bahar (2), 1965-1988 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Irian Bahar (3), 1985-1988 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Tapol etc. (1), 1965-1991 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    Newspaper clippings (1965); 1977-8; original notes; news publications (1967; 1991); typescripts (1966; 1973; 1978); scanned news articles (1977); some marginalia
  - Misc. Tapol etc. (2) (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Zaman Olanda, 1950-1983 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Typescript; some marginalia (1950); scanned typescripts (1899; 1981); scanned article (1983)
  - Minangkabau history/culture papers/seminar, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Reprint (1970); typescripts (1970)
  - Murba/Tanm Bahan, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    Typescripts (1989); scanned news articles (1989)
  - Mystical Movements, 1969-1974 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    Scanned typescript (1974); news report (1969)
  - Non - Blok, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    Scanned typescripts (1992)
  - Pakem/Aliran, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    Image; statistical charts with marginalia; scanned data sheets; Typed manuscripts carbon copy (1963)
  - Parties/Organizations, 1966-1987 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    Scanned typescripts (1987); table chart (1966)
  - Political Prisoners (Indonesia), 1988-1993 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    Reprint (1993); scanned typescripts (1988; 1990-1)
  - Saminism, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    Typed manuscript copies (1964)
  - Students - KAMI Stuff, 1966-1967 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    Notes; typescripts (1965-7)
  - Students 1990s, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    Official reports (1994)
  - Sumartono: Indonesia Under Fascism, Undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
    Mimeographed typescript
  - Underground, Undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
    Collection of correspondence, reports, etc. (1991); scanned news articles (1991); other typescripts; scanned news report (1989)
  - US Embassy Translation, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    Typescripts (1974-5)
  - Ali Moertopo, Undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
    Typescript copy
  - Arm Aid to Indonesia (1), 1968-1986 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    Scanned news articles and charts (1968 - 1970; 1975; 1977; 1982); reports and bulletins (1977; 1986); US government legislative. doc. (1976); memorandum (1974); original typed notes
  - Arm Aid to Indonesia (2), 1968-1986 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Arms Aid II (1) (Box 34, Folder 5)
    Scanned reports and other typescripts (1974-9; 1981); sales listings and charts; scanned news articles (1980; 1982)
  - Arms Aid II (2) (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Army Positions, 1965-1970 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    Typescripts (1970); charts (1965); handwritten notes
  - Benson Materials on Civic Mission, 1962-1964 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    Typescripts (1962; 1964); photographs, some with descriptions (1964)
  - Bunnell's Army, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    Typescript drafts (1974)
  - Dharsono Pleidooi, 1985-1986 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    Scanned typescripts (1985-6)
  - Intel, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Typescript drafts (1988)
  - Military Elites Data (1), 1972-1989 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    Newspaper clippings (1972; 1992); scanned news articles (1985); original notes, especially regarding military personnel; various typescripts (1964; 1984; 1989); marginalia
  - Military Elites Data: Seskoad Foreign Training (2), 1964-1966 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Military Elites Training (3), 1988 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Military Elites Data: Indonesia Drafts (4), 1987-1988 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Military - Ideology, 1979-1982 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    Typescripts, scanned and originals (1979; 1982)
  - M. Sadi: Influence of the Military on Economic Development: An Analysis, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    Typescript draft (1964)
  - Nasution and Davifungei Stuff, 1960-1991 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    Interview transcript (1991); Typscript (1960; 1969); news publication (1970)
  - Notes and Clippings, 1963-1976 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    Notes (some extensively handwritten); typescripts (1963; 1974); table chart (1966); scanned news articles (1976)
  - Pengarahan Pangdam Jaya and Kopestis IIII, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Rancangan Undang Military, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    Scanned typescripts (1982)
  - Seminar Ad Ke - II/1965, 1965-1966 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    Typescripts (1965-6)
  - Elite Military, 1969-1988 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    Correspondence (1983); report (1986); typescripts (1969; 1984-5); biographical information/notes with additional comments; various notes; scanned news articles (1985; 1987-8); military personnel information
  - Military Photographs, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    Photographs and newspaper clipping with descriptions (circa 1963); portraits on print
- Series II. Thailand
  - PKT Tample Shill, including photo 1, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Images; various typescripts; scanned newspaper publication
  - Miscellaneous Texts and Bibliographies, 1955-1989 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    Bibliography; obituary (1976); typescript (1989); Election poll data; small, typed biography (1955); typescript (1970); interview excerpts (1977); translated newspaper article
  - Thai Bankers 1, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    Typescript (1987)
  - Thai Army, Undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
    Scanned typescript with marginalia (also scanned)
  - September 9th, 1985: 1, 1985-09-01 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    Scanned typescript with attached manuscript (1985); posters
  - October 14th Stuff: 1, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Newspapers (1973; 1974)
  - October 6th Stuff, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Typescripts, including letters (1976; 1977); scanned typescripts; scanned typescript with marginalia; poster (2 copies); scanned flowchart; news brief (1977); images (1976)
  - Batson on October 6th, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    Typescript (1977)
  - October 6th, 1976 Bahan Dafler 1, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    Draft typescript (1976); typescripts (1976); scanned typescript (1976) reprint article (1976); manuscript (1977); news publications (1976-7); scanned newspaper (1976-7); newspapers; posters
  - Chik Nakak Sakdina Thai Translation, Undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Declassified Docs, 1940-1950 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Declassified Docs, 1960-1970 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Thais: Papers and Politics, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    Typescripts (1988); typescript draft (1987); typescript with marginalia
  - Thailand Miscellaneous Socio-political 1, 1967-1988 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    typescript draft (1980); scanned typescript (1984); typescript (1977; 1979; 1983; 1988); newspaper (1978-9); statistical data (1977); news publication (1967; 1975; 1977); poster
  - Thailand Miscellaneous Socio-political 2, 1967-1988 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Leitenburg Press Clippings (Box 25, Folder 21)
    U.S. publication index cutouts and summaries; news publication indexes; research notes and article summaries
  - Thailand - Political Prisoners, etc. Human Rights, 1977-1989 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    Typescripts (1977; 1979; 1988); news publication; letters (1984); scanned news articles (1989); typescript draft (1985); biographical information (1983); correspondence (1980)
  - R VI, 1917-02 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    Typescript (1917)
  - Thailand - Opium, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    Scanned news article (1976); news publication (1977); typescript
  - Own Notes, 1974-1977 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    Manuscript; typescripts (1974); personal notes on scholarly papers
  - Military 1, 1959-1988 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    Handwritten notes; personal notes on scholarly paper; scanned manuscript (1976); typescript drafts (1967; 1970); typescripts (1975; 1977; 1982; 1984 1988); scanned typescript with marginalia; typescript drafts (1982; 1985); news publication (1986); U.S. government publications (1959; 1962); Thai government publication (1985); scanned news article (1975; 1977; 1984; 1986); newspapers (1977; 1981); magazines (1977)
  - Military 2, 1975-1986 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Warin/Trocki Papers on Politics, 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Muslims in Thailand, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    Typescript - possible draft (1987)
  - Miscellaneous Thai Historical Bahan, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Typescripts (1942; 1988); scanned typescript (1983); index of journal articles
  - Thai Regional Problems, 1979-1985 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    Typescripts - possibly unpublished (1979; 1985); scanned typescript
  - Thailand Research Materials 1975, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    Notes, written and typed; statistical data sheets of wide variety of context
  - Local Tip Baman, 1977-1988 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    News publication (1977-8)
  - Thai Literature, 1975-1980 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    Correspondence; typescripts (1975; 1980); notes
  - Choltira Baman, 1975-1977 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    Scanned typescripts (1975; 1977)
  - JIT File, 1975-1980 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    Interview transcripts (1975; 1977; 1980); personal notes on testimony (1978); reprint (1975); news article (1977); scanned news article (1978)
  - Phillips Stuff, Undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
    Typescripts
  - My Thai Book, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    Typed notes, on scholarly works and otherwise; typescript (1983)
  - Charnvit Writings, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    Typescripts; journal article (1976); scanned typescript
  - S. P. Pt. IV, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    Various scanned typescripts (1973-4
  - Sanakomsat Part I, 1963-1972 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    Typed notes; scanned typescripts, some with marginalia (1963-72)
  - Sanakomsat Part II, 1969-1971 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    Various scanned typescripts (1969-1971)
  - Sanakomsat Part III, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    Typescript with notes (1973); scanned typescript (1972-3)
  - Thailand: Typed Notes for Book, 1957-1977 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    scanned typescript (1974); notes on scholarly publications (1957; 1965; 1974; 1977; etc.)
  - Declassified Docs 45:50 Thailand, 1950-1983 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Declassified Docs 45:50 Thailand
  - In the Mirror Proofs, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    In the Mirror Proofs
  - Mattani Thai Lit, 1976-1978 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Mattani Thai Lit
  - Misc Thai materials, Undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Misc Thai materials
  - Papers on Thai Economy, Undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Papers on Thai Economy
  - Saneh Rangsan Social Science Review 76, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Saneh Rangsan Social Science Review 76
  - Thailand Prisoners, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Thailand Prisoners
  - Truong Case, 1976-1978 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Truong Case
- Series III. Philippines
  - Philippines - U.S., 1980-1988 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    Thesis (1988); typescripts (1980;1987-8)
  - Underground Philippines Materials, 1975-1988 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    Typescripts (1976; 1988); scanned journal publications (1975)
  - Papers: 1 of 2, 1970-1988 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    Typescripts (1986-7; 1970; 1977; 1988); typescript drafts (1985, 1988; 1992); typescript with notes, multiple copies (1975)
  - Papers: 2 of 2, 1970-1988 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Agrarians, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    Scanned newspaper (1988); typescripts (1987); statistical data
  - Aquino (1), Undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Aquino (2), Undated (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Cartoons, Undated (Box 24, Folder 22)
    Scanned image; scanned newspaper
  - "Kliping", 1970-1987 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    Newspapers (1970; 1972; 1987; 1992); scanned news articles (1987); news publications (1986-7); government publication
  - Philosophy, Literature, Art, Undated (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Typescript; bibliography
  - Moro, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    Scanned typescript (1976); thesis
  - Marcos', 1972-1987 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    Correspondence (1972); typescript draft (1975); newspapers (1978; 1987); journal publication (1986); scanned news article (1987)
  - Notes, 1972-1980 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    Personal notes and questions on scholarly papers; possible lecture notes, some with additional annotations
  - Philippines - NPA, Anti - Lava Tract, Undated (Box 24, Folder 28)
    typescript (1971)
- Series IV. Malaysia
  - Fuemsso, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    English-language newspapers (1977 - 1978)
  - Malaysia and Singapore materials and offprints (1), 1982-05-10-1982-05-14 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    Typescript (1982)
  - Bangsawan, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    Typescript, two copies, one with editorial comments, one without (1988)
  - Literacy and Epic in the Malay World, Undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Typescript with marginalia (1980s (exact date unknown))
  - Miscellaneous Malaysia - articles, etc., 1969-1989 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    Typescripts, two with marginalia, one without (1988); newspaper (1969); scanned publication; correspondence (1989)
- Series V. Miscellaneous documents and course material
  - Culture and Politics Correspondence, 1963-1967 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Typescripts (letters from dates specified in file title)
  - Culture and Politics Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Culture and Politics - AS Minutes, Memos, Etc., 1964-1969 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    Typescripts (1964 - 1969)